Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Information Center Vertical Files, 1916-1999
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files
  - Fruits-Melons (Box 71)
  - Fruits-Oranges (Box 72)
  - Fruits-Peaches (Box 72)
  - Fruits-Pears (Box 72)
  - Fruits-Persimmons (Box 72)
  - Fruits-Pineapples (Box 72)
  - Fruits-Pomegranates (Box 72)
  - Fruits-Prunes (Box 72)
  - Fruits-Rhubarb (Box 72)
  - Furniture and Furnishings (Box 72)
  - Future (Box 72)
  - Game as a Food (Box 72)
  - Games (Box 72)
  - Games-Pinball (Box 72)
  - Games-Video Games, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box 72)
  - Games-Video Games, (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box 73)
  - Gardens, (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Gelatin (Box 73)
  - Genealogy (Box 73)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 73)
  - Glass and Glassware (Box 73)
  - Gold (Box 73)
  - Grain (Box 73)
  - Grains, 1990s, (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Greeting Cards (Box 74)
  - Grocery Stores-Convenience (Box 74)
  - Grocery Stores-Delivery (Box 74)
  - Grocery Stores-Food Service Departments (Box 74)
  - Grocery Stores-Hypermarkets (Box 74)
  - Grocery Stores-Sales (Box 74)
  - Grocery Stores-Supermarkets (Box 74)
  - Hair (Box 74)
  - Hair Care-Beauty Shops (Box 74)
  - Hardware Industry and Trade (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Appliances (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Bath Products (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Feminine Hygiene Products (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty-Fragrances (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Hands and Nails (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-History, (2 folders) (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Hypoallergenic (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Industry and Trade, (2 folders) (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Skin Care, 1980s, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 75)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Skin Care, 1980s, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 76)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Skin Care, 1990s (Box 76)
  - Health and Beauty Aids-Suntan Preparations (Box 76)
  - Health and Exercise (Box 76)
  - Health and Exercise-Equipment (Box 76)
  - Heart Disease (Box 76)
  - Highways (Box 76)
  - Hispanic Americans (Box 76)
  - Holidays (Box 76)
  - Holidays-The Family Album (Box 76)
  - Holidays-Chinese (Box 77)
  - Holidays-Christmas, (5 folders) (Box 77)
  - Holidays-Easter (Box 77)
  - Holidays-Fourth of July (Box 77)
  - Holidays-Halloween (Box 78)
  - Holidays-Thanksgiving (Box 78)
  - Holidays-Valentine’s Day (Box 78)
  - Holography (Box 78)
  - Home Based Work (Box 78)
  - Honey (Box 78)
  - Hospitals (Box 78)
  - Hotels, (4 folders) (Box 78)
  - Housing, 1970-1978, (2 folders) (Box 79)
  - Housing, (1-5 of 8 folders) (Box 79)
  - Housing, (6-8 of 8 folders) (Box 80)
  - Ice Cream, (5 folders) (Box 80)
  - Ice Cream-Flavors (Box 81)
  - Ice Cream-Historical Data (Box 81)
  - Ice Cream-Ice Bars (Box 81)
  - Ice Cream-Statistics (Box 81)
  - Illinois Department of Employment Security-IL Labor Market Review (Box 81)
  - Illinois Department of Employment Security-IL Monthly Statistical Summary (Box 81)
  - Income, Consumer, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box 81)
  - Income, Consumer, (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box 82)
  - Income-National (GNP) (Box 82)
  - Income Tax, (4 folders) (Box 82)
  - Insecticides (Box 82)
  - Insurance-Automobile (Box 82)
  - Insurance-Business (Box 82)
  - Insurance-Health (Box 82)
  - Insurance-Life, (2 folders) (Box 83)
  - Insurance-Miscellaneous (Box 83)
  - International Advertising Association (Box 83)
  - Integrated Marketing (Box 83)
  - International Trade-Asia (Box 83)
  - International Trade-Asia-China (Box 83)
  - International Trade-Canada (Box 83)
  - International Trade-Europe, 1990s (Box 83)
  - Internet, (1-2 of 7 folders) (Box 83)
  - Internet, (3-7 of 7 folders) (Box 84)
  - Inventions and Inventors, (2 folders) (Box 84)
  - Japan (Box 84)
  - Jewelry Industry & Trade (Box 85)
  - Jewelry Industry & Trade-Diamonds (Box 85)
  - Jewish Market-Customs (Box 85)
  - Labor Force (Box 85)
  - Laundry Products (Box 85)
  - Law (Box 85)
  - Leisure Market, (3 folders) (Box 85)
  - Leisure Market-Work Week, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Libraries, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Life Span (Box 86)
  - Light Productions-Prior to 1990 (Box 86)
  - Light Productions, 1990s (Box 86)
  - Living Cost, (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Living Costs, (2 folders) (Box 87)
  - (See Also: U.S. Department of Labor) (Box 87)
  - Living Habits-Articles, 1990s (Box 87)
  - Lunch (Box 87)
  - Luxury Market (Box 87)
  - Macaroni Products (Box 87)
  - Macaroni Products-History (Box 87)
  - Magazines-Advertising (Box 87)
  - Magic (Box 87)
  - Mail Order Business (Box 87)
  - Malt Beverages, (2 folders) (Box 88)
  - Malt Beverages-Advertising, (1-5 of 6 folders) (Box 88)
  - Malt Beverages-Advertising, (6 of 6 folders) (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-Bock Beer (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-Consumption (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-Cookery (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-Draft Beer (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-Dry (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-History, (3 folders) (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-Ice Beer (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-Imported Beer, Prior to 1980s, (1 of 3 folders) (Box 89)
  - Malt Beverages-Imported Beer, Prior to 1980s, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box 90)
  - Malt Beverages-Imported Beer, 1980s, (2 folders) (Box 90)
  - Malt Beverages-Imported Beer, 1990s (Box 90)
  - Malt Beverages-Industry and Trade, Prior to 1980, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box 90)
  - Malt Beverages-Industry and Trade, Prior to 1980, (3 of 3 folders) (Box 91)
  - Malt Beverages-Industry and Trade, 1980s (Box 91)
  - Malt Beverages-Industry and Trade, 1990s (Box 91)
  - Malt Beverages-International Aspects (Box 91)
  - Malt Beverages-Low Calorie, (2 folders) (Box 91)
  - Malt Beverages-Packaging (Box 91)
  - Malt Beverages-Premium Beers (Box 91)
  - Malt Beverages-Statistics (Box 91)
  - Malt Beverages-Technical Aspects (Box 91)
  - Margarine (Box 92)
  - Marketing-Success Stories (Box 92)
  - (See Also: Advertising-Positioning; & Advertising-Success Stories) (Box 92)
  - Marriage (Box 92)
  - Mature Market (Box 92)
  - Meals-Lunches (Box 92)
  - (See Also: Lunch) (Box 92)
  - Meat (Box 92)
  - Meat, Beef (Box 92)
  - Meat, Canned (Box 92)
  - Meat, Consumption (Box 92)
  - Meat-Cookery (Box 92)
  - Meat-Frankfurters (Box 92)
  - Meat, Ham (Box 92)
  - Meat-Industry (Box 92)
  - Meat-Nutritional Value (Box 92)
  - Meat-Pork, (2 folders) (Box 92)
  - Meat-Sausage (Box 93)
  - Medical Care (Box 93)
  - Middle-Age Market (45-64) (Box 93)
  - Military Market, (2 folders) (Box 93)
  - Milk (Box 93)
  - Milk-Additives (Box 93)
  - Milk-Consumption (Box 93)
  - Milk-Distribution (Box 93)
  - Milk, Evaporated (Box 93)
  - Milk Industry Foundation-Milk Facts (5 Years) (Box 93)
  - Milk-Nutritional Value (Box 94)
  - (See Also: Misc. Data on Consumption Facts) (Box 94)
  - Monosodium Glutamate (Box 94)
  - Motion Picture Industry & Trade (Box 94)
  - Motorcycles (Box 94)
  - Moving (Box 94)
  - Mushrooms-Includes Truffles) (Box 94)
  - Music (Box 94)
  - Music-Country Music (Box 94)
  - Music-Jukeboxes (Box 94)
  - Musical Instruments (Box 94)
  - Mustard (Box 94)
  - Names (Box 94)
  - NASCAR (Box 94)
  - National Dairy Council-Dairy Council Digest, 1973-1979 (Box 94)
  - National Dairy Council-Dairy Council Digest, 1982-19851982-1993, (2 folders) (Box 95)
  - National Dairy Council-Dairy Council Digest, 1994+1994 on (Box 95)
  - Native Americans, (2 folders) (Box 95)
  - Newspapers (Box 95)
  - Newspapers-Advertising Expenditures (Box 95)
  - Newspapers-FSIs (Box 95)
  - Niche Marketing (Box 95)
  - Nielsen, A.C.-Drug (Box 95)
  - Nielsen, A.C.-Grocery (Box 95)
  - Nutrition (Box 95)
  - (See Also: Vitamins; Food-Nutritive Value; & Advertising Appeals-Health) (Box 95)
  - Nuts (Box 96)
  - Odors (Box 96)
  - Office Products (Box 96)
  - Olives and Olive Oil (Box 96)
  - Outdoor Advertising (Box 96)
  - Packaging (Box 96)
  - Packaging-Food, 1990s (Box 96)
  - Paper Products (Box 96)
  - Peanut Butter (Box 96)
  - Pens (Box 96)
  - Pesticides (Box 96)
  - (See Also: Insecticides) (Box 96)
  - Pet Food (Box 96)
  - Pet Food-Statistics (Box 96)
  - Pets (Box 96)
  - Photography (Box 96)
  - Pickles (Box 96)
  - (See Also: Condiments) (Box 96)
  - Pizza, 1990s (Box 96)
  - Plastics (Box 96)
  - Point of Purchase Advertising, (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - Popcorn (Box 96)
  - Population (Box 97)
  - Potato Chips (Box 97)
  - Pregnancy, (2 folders) (Box 97)
  - Pretzels (Box 97)
  - Prices (Box 97)
  - Prices-EDLP, (2 folders) (Box 97)
  - Print Advertising-Costs (Box 97)
  - Products-Certification (Box 97)
  - Products-Claims (Box 97)
  - Products-Established (Box 97)
  - Products, Names for (Box 97)
  - Products, New (Box 97)
  - Products, New-Development (Box 97)
  - Products, New-Introduction (Box 97)
  - Products, New-Management (Box 97)
  - Products, New-Mortality (Box 97)
  - Products, Quality (Box 98)
  - Psychology (Box 98)
  - Public Opinion Polls (Box 98)
  - Public Opinion Poll-“The Public Pulse,” 1992-1999, (10 folders) (Box 98)
  - Public Relations (Box 98)
  - Quality, (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Radio (Box 99)
  - Radio Advertising Bureau (Box 99)
  - Radio Commercials (Box 99)
  - Railroads (Box 99)
  - Railroads-Historical (Box 99)
  - Real Estate (Box 99)
  - Recreation-Gambling & Lotteries (Box 99)
  - Relationship Marketing (Box 99)
  - Restaurants (Box 99)
  - Restaurants-Famous & Historical, (2 folders) (Box 100)
  - Restaurants-Fast Food (Box 100)
  - Retail (Box 100)
  - Rice (Box 100)
  - Rubber (Box 100)
  - Salad Dressing, (3 folders) (Box 100)
  - Salads, (2 folders) (Box 101)
  - Sales Promotion, 1990 (Box 101)
  - Sales Promotion-Annuals, (1-4 of 8 folders) (Box 101)
  - Sales Promotion-Annuals, (5-8 of 8 folders) (Box 102)
  - Sales Promotion-Continuity (Box 102)
  - Sales Promotion-Samples (Box 102)
  - Sales Promotion-Telephones (Box 102)
  - Salt (Box 102)
  - Sandwiches, (2 folders) (Box 102)
  - (See Also: Meals) (Box 102)
  - Sandwiches, 1980 on (Box 103)
  - (See Also: Meals) (Box 103)
  - Sauces & Sauce Mixes, (2 folders) (Box 103)
  - Sex Habits (Box 103)
  - Shoes-History (Box 103)
  - Shopping Centers (Box 103)
  - Sleep (Box 103)
  - Soap (Box 103)
  - Soft Drinks-Advertising, 1982 (Box 103)
  - Soft Drinks (Box 103)
  - Solar Energy (Box 103)
  - Soup (Box 103)
  - Space, (1 of 4 folders) (Box 103)
  - Space, (2-4 of 4 folders) (Box 104)
  - Spices & Herbs, (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Sponsorship, (2 folders) (Box 104)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods, (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Baseball, (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Football, (3 folders) (Box 105)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Golf (Box 106)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Olympics, to 1980, (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Olympics, 1980-1984, (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Olympics, 1984, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box 106)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Olympics, 1984, (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box 107)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Olympics, 1988-1996, (5 folders) (Box 107)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Pan-American Games (Box 107)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Statistics (Box 107)
  - Sports & Sporting Goods-Super Bowl (Box 107)
  - Steel (Box 108)
  - Sugar & Sugar Substitutes (Box 108)
  - Superstitions (Box 108)
  - Symbols, (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Syrup, (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Taste (Box 108)
  - Taste, Aesthetic (Box 108)
  - Tattoos & Tattooing (Box 108)
  - Tea (Box 108)
  - Telecommunications-Fiberoptics (Box 108)
  - Telecommunications-Papers (Box 108)
  - Telecommunications-Service Providers, Local & Long-distance (Box 108)
  - Telecommunications-The Yankee Group Research for Strategic Decisions-Data Communications (Box 109)
  - Telecommunications-The Yankee Group-1996 TAF Survey (Box 109)
  - Telecommunications-The Yankee Group Research for Strategic Decisions-Telecommunications (Box 109)
  - Telecommunications-The Yankee Group Research for Strategic Decisions-Wireless/Mobile, (3 folders) (Box 109)
  - Telecommunications-Yankee Watch-Consumer Communications, (3 folders) (Box 110)
  - Telecommunications-Yankee Watch-Data Communications (Box 110)
  - Telecommunications-Yankee Watch-Internet Data Strategies (Box 110)
  - Telecommunications-Yankee Watch-Telecommunications (Box 110)
  - Telecommunications-Yankee Watch-Wireless/Mobile Communications, (2 folders) (Box 110)
  - Telephones (Box 111)
  - Telephones-Answering Devices (Box 111)
  - Telephones-Cellular (Mobile), (3 folders) (Box 111)
  - Telephones-Long Distance (Box 111)
  - Television Advertising (Box 111)
  - Television Advertising-Commercials, 1980 on (Box 111)
  - Television Advertising-Commercials-Children (Box 111)
  - Television Advertising-Commercials-Costs, (3 folders) (Box 112)
  - Television Advertising-Commercials-Infomercials, (1-3 of 6 folders) (Box 112)
  - Television Advertising-Commercials-Infomercials, (4-6 of 6 folders) (Box 113)
  - Television Advertising-Commercials-Length (Box 113)
  - Television Advertising-Commercials-Video Storyboard Survey, (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Television Advertising-Interactive (Box 113)
  - Television Audiences (Box 113)
  - Television Audiences-Children-Articles, 1990 (Box 113)
  - (See Also: Television Advertising-Commercials-Children; & Television Programs-Children’s) (Box 113)
  - Television-Cable, 1990s (Box 113)
  - Television-History, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Television-History, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 114)
  - Television Information Office Releases (Box 114)
  - Television Programs-Children’s, (3 folders) (Box 114)
  - (See Also: Television Audiences-Children; & Television Advertising-Commercials-Children) (Box 114)
  - Television-Rating Services (Box 114)
  - Television Sets (Box 114)
  - Testimonials, 1980, (1 of 3 folders) (Box 114)
  - Testimonials, 1980, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box 115)
  - Time Magazine-Releases, (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Tobacco (Box 115)
  - Tofu (Box 115)
  - Tools (Box 115)
  - Toothbrushes (Box 115)
  - Toys, 1985 on (Box 116)
  - (See Also: Games) (Box 116)
  - Trade Characters, 1980 on, (3 folders) (Box 116)
  - Trademarks (Box 116)
  - Trade names (Box 116)
  - (See Also: Corporate Image) (Box 116)
  - Travel (Box 116)
  - Travel, (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Travel-Business (Box 117)
  - Travel-Cruises, (3 folders) (Box 117)
  - Travel-International (Box 117)
  - Travel-Outlook for Travel & Tourism, 1990, 1995-1999, (6 folders) (Box 118)
  - Travel-Special Reports, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 118)
  - Travel-Special Reports, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 119)
  - Travel-Survey of State Travel Offices, 1993-1997, (2 folders) (Box 119)
  - Travel-Tourism Works for America (Box 119)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Association of America, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box 119)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Association of America, (3 of 3 folders) (Box 120)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Association of America-Directory, 1999 (Box 120)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Association of America-Economic Review of Travel in America (Box 120)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Association of America-Impact of Travel on State Economies, 1992-1997 (Box 120)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Association of America-Newsline, (2 folders) (Box 120)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Association of America-Traveler Profiles, (2 folders) (Box 121)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Association of America-Travelometer (Box 121)
  - Travel-Travel Industry Talking Points (Box 121)
  - Travel-Travel Industry World Yearbook, 1986-1994, (4 folders) (Box 121)
  - Travel-Travel Industry World Yearbook, 1995-1998, (2 folders) (Box 122)
  - Travel-Travel Market Report, 1993-1997, (5 folders) (Box 122)
  - Travel-Travel Market Report, 1998 (Box 123)
  - Travel-Travel & Technology (Box 123)
  - Travel-Travelometer (Box 123)
  - Travel-U. S., (4 folders) (Box 123)
  - Umbrellas (Box 124)
  - USDA-National Food Review, (1-6 of 12 folders) (Box 124)
  - USDA-National Food Review, (7-12 of 12 folders) (Box 125)
  - USDA-Food Review (Box 126)
  - USDHHS-Monthly Vital Statistics Report, (2 folders) (Box 126)
  - U. S.-Dept. of Labor (Box 126)
  - United States-Historical, (1-2 of 5 folders) (Box 126)
  - United States-Historical, (3-5 of 5 folders) (Box 127)
  - United States-Money (Box 127)
  - U. S.-Navy (Box 127)
  - Vegetables, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 127)
  - Vegetables, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 128)
  - Vending Machines (Box 128)
  - Vinegar (Box 128)
  - Vitamins (Box 128)
  - Wine (Box 128)
  - Wine-Advertising (Box 128)
  - Wine-California, (2 folders) (Box 128)
  - Wine-Champagne & Sparkling Wines (Box 129)
  - Wine-Cookery (Box 129)
  - Wine-France (Box 129)
  - Wine Industry & Trade, (2 folders) (Box 129)
  - Women, 1980 on (Box 129)
  - Women-Advertising Aspects, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 129)
  - Women-Advertising Aspects, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 130)
  - Women Workers, (2 folders) (Box 130)
  - Wood & Wood Products, (2 folders) (Box 130)
  - Wool (Box 130)
  - Yogurt, 1980s, (2 folders) (Box 131)
  - Yogurt, 1990s (Box 131)
  - Yogurt-Frozen, (2 folders) (Box 131)
  - Young Adult Market, (2 folders) (Box 131)
  - Youth Market (Box 131)
  - Youth Market-Children, (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - Youth Market-Generation X (Baby Busters), (3 folders) (Box 132)
  - Youth Market-Generation Y (Box 132)
  - Youth Markets-Teenagers, 1990s (Box 132)
  - Zoos (Box 132)
- Justin White Files
  - Advertising agencies--client relations, (4 folders) (Box 133)
  - Advertising agencies--client relations--Agency of record (Box 133)
  - Advertising agencies--client relations--printed materials, (2 folders) (Box 133)
  - Advertising agencies--client relations--Tenure, (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Advertising agencies--client relations--Tenure--Movement of accounts to independent or house agencies (Box 134)
  - Advertising agencies--Personnel--Articles, (3 folders) (Box 134)
  - Advertising agencies--Personnel--Compensation, (1 of 4 folders) (Box 134)
  - Advertising agencies--Personnel--Compensation, (2-4 of 4 folders) (Box 135)
  - Advertising agencies--Personnel--Minority employment, 1969-1981 (Box 135)
  - Advertising agencies--Personnel--Salaries, (3 folders) (Box 135)
  - Advertising and marketing bibliography, 1997 (Box 136)
  - Advertising: booklets (General Mills: Facts of Progress, 1936; General Mills: What's Back of Our Jobs? 1936; Institute of Life Insurance: Everyman's Primer of Life Insurance, 1939), 1936, 1939 (Box 136)
  - Advertising: Case for Advertising (JWT London), 1976 (Box 136)
  - Advertising: Copies of articles on agency income, 1987-1991 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 136)
  - Advertising--Economic aspects, (3 folders) (Box 136)
  - Advertising--Economic aspects--Printed material, (1 of 5 folders) (Box 136)
  - Advertising--Economic aspects--Printed material, (2-5 of 5 folders) (Box 137)
  - Advertising--Economic aspects--Prices (Box 137)
  - Advertising--Economic aspects--Recession, (1 of 5 folders) (Box 137)
  - Advertising--Economic aspects--Recession, (2-5 of 5 folders) (Box 138)
  - Advertising--Economic aspects--Securities values (Box 138)
  - Advertising--King Papers (JWT London, 1988); Many Worlds of Sam Meek (1981) (Box 138)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy (Box 138)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing, (1 of 3 folders) (Box 138)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box 139)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Pre-testing (Box 139)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Pre-testing--Psychometric methods (Box 139)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Pre-testing--Townsend & Townsend (Box 139)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 139)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 140)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership--Business papers, (2 folders) (Box 140)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership--Methods, (3 folders) (Box 140)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership--Methods--Nielsen (1963); Research Foundation (1962) (Box 140)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership--Methods--Politz (1967); AMRB (1972) (Box 140)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership--Newspapers, (3 folders) (Box 141)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership--Printed material, (1-3 of 5 folders) (Box 141)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership--Printed material, (4-5 of 5 folders) (Box 142)
  - Advertising--Research--Copy testing--Readership--Starch tested copy (Box 142)
  - Advertising--Seals of Approval--Good Housekeeping, (2 folders) (Box 142)
  - Advertising--Seals of Approval--Parents' Magazine (Box 142)
  - Advertising--Spending (Robert Coen, McCann-Erickson) (Box 143)
  - Advertising--Techniques--Comparative, 1990-1995, (2 folders) (Box 143)
  - Advertising--Types--Multi-product (Box 143)
  - Advertising--Types--Testimonial, (1-4 of 5 folders) (Box 143)
  - Advertising--Types--Testimonial, (5 of 5 folders) (Box 144)
  - Billboard Top Popular Records of the Year, 1946-1985, (3 folders) (Box 144)
  - Hot Creative Shop (Box 144)
  - Improvement of Information Retrieval in JWT (Albert Stridsberg), 1970 (Box 144)
  - Improving Advertising Budgeting (AAAA), 1998 (Box 144)
  - Information Center Report, 1962 (Box 144)
  - Information Resources Inventory, 1980 (Box 144)
  - Joel Whitburn's Pop Annual, 1974-1976 (Box 144)
  - JWT history, 1974-1989 (Box 144)
  - Managing and Mastering Change (Roper Starch), 1998 (Box 144)
  - Morning in America (Box 145)
  - Organization at JWT, 1916-1990, (1-11 of 24 folders) (Box 145)
  - Organization at JWT, 1916-1990, (12-24 of 24 folders) (Box 146)
  - Organization at JWT--New York Office, (1-2 of 5 folders) (Box 146)
  - Organization at JWT--New York Office, (3-5 of 5 folders) (Box 147)
  - Organization at JWT--New York Office--New business (Box 147)
  - Organization at JWT--New York Office--Representatives (Box 147)
  - Sources of Information on European Countries (JWT London), 1969 (Box 147)
  - Technique for Producing Ideas (James Webb Young), 1960 (Box 147)
  - What's Cooking: A Perspective on Eating in America, 1996 (Box 147)
  - WPP, 1988-1991 (Box 147)
  - WPP/Ogilvy, 1989 (Box 147)
  - Yankelovich Monitor Data Run, 1999 (Box 147)